nokiasymbianthemes.com 2012-05-13

# Privacy Policy of Nokia Symbian Themes Blog | Nokia Symbian Themes

Browse >[Home](http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/ "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy

COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

This site is owned and operated by [Ishtiaq Saddam](http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/about) who is the CEO of Chaos Inc. or Nokia Symbian Themes located under the domain http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com and if you have any questions or queries regarding our privacy policy then feel free to contact us through our contact page.

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Nokia Symbian Themes, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we sometimes gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

INFORMATION NOKIA SYMBIAN THEMES GATHERS AND TRACKS

Nokia Symbian Themes gathers two types of information about users:

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our post comments, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys, to personalize your experience, improve our site, improve our content promotions etc.
  * Information Nokia Symbian Themes gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and which in turn help our potential advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because Nokia Symbian Themes derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. Under no circumstances does Nokia Symbian Themes divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.
  * Optionally our ad networks and content partners can collect information to process transactions at their end.  

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested given the URL http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com is displayed on the address field of the browser when doing the transactions.

 **Nokia Symbian Themes Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:**

 ** _Optional Voluntary Information:_** We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or submit a comment.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• Optionally to process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or any site updates..

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We and our content partner MobiHand implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. Please take a look at the store policy further down the page for all that details.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our partner’s () Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toï¿½keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers as that part of the transaction is not committed to our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Nokia Symbian Themes does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We also may use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) in the future.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, DoubleClick, TribalFusion, ADSDAQ, Comission Junction etc to name a few at the present time, however more advertising and premium content partners must also be considered to be goverend under the policies even though they are not exclusively mentioned here. We are also a premium and exclusive partner of MobiHand Inc.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Nokia Symbian Themes send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Nokia Symbian Themes has no access to or control over these cookies (cookies placed by either our advertising partners and content partners) that are used by third-party advertisers through our advertising partners.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Nokia Symbian Themes’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Also please note that for advertisements generated by our advertising partners, we require you to agree to the following:

Our third party vendor can and may use cookies to serve ads on our site.

Our advertising partner Google Adsense & DoubleClick ([DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.com/) is a division of [Google Inc](http://www.google.com/)., which annually certifies itself for the European Union-United States Safe Harbor program. Such certification covers the activities of DoubleClick, and the obligations of the safe harbor program apply to any personal information about European visitors that is stored on their servers in the United States.) uses the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) which enables them to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by [visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you wish to disable cookies (all cookies), you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others legal rights, property, or safety. However, random, non-personally identifiable visitor information (e.g. out of 100 people how many liked this post or that post and so on) may be provided to other parties for development, marketing, advertising etc. purposes. Don’t worry though, rest assured we still never share information of our valued users to anyone.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Log In’ page located at http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/wp-login.php

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **E-Mail to a Friend Policy**

Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking “Share This”. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose and you are really thanked by me if you do it.

 **Store Policy**

This policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of our products and services.

> What This (Store) Privacy Policy Covers.
> 
> This policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of our products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
> 
> This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.
> 
> Information Collection and Use
> 
> General
> 
> We collect personal information when you register with us, when you use or buy our products or services, when you visit our pages or the pages of certain partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. we may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
> 
> When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with us and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
> 
> We collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.
> 
> We use information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
> 
> We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
> 
> Many downloadable software applications that we sell require the software developers to provide the customer with a registration code to convert trial versions into full versions. In these cases, we must provide the software developers with relevant customer information in order for them to generate a registration code and email it to the customer. Although we strongly encourage software developers to follow strict privacy policies, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices that each of the software companies follow. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain developer or software company, you may contact them directly or visit their individual web sites.
> 
> We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with us under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from us and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
> 
> We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
> 
> We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
> 
> We transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
> 
> We do not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
> 
> Cookies
> 
> We may set and access cookies on your computer. Cookies are small information files stored by your browser on your hard drive that allow us to provide advanced features such as content and shopping cart personalization. The cookies we use do not contain any personal information. If you wish, you can change your browser settings to disable cookies, but please note that cookies must be enabled on your browser in order to make a purchase at our web site.
> 
> Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
> 
> General
> 
> You can edit your Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
> 
> We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the service, such as service announcements or administrative messages, that are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
> 
> Confidentiality and Security
> 
> We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
> 
> Changes to this Privacy Policy
> 
> We may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
> 
> Questions and Suggestions
> 
> If you have any questions and comments about our Privacy Policy please contact our customer support.

 **Nokia Symbian Themes Content Policy** (Chaos Inc. the developed exclusive Themes, Games and Applications and the Posts, Images, Multimedia & Other Miscellaneous Files)

Many downloadable software applications that we sell or provide free require the software developers to provide the customer with a registration code to convert trial versions into full versions. In these cases, we must provide the software developers with relevant customer information in order for them to generate a registration code and email it to the customer. Although we strongly encourage software developers to follow strict privacy policies, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices that each of the software companies follow. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain developer or software company, you may contact them directly or visit their individual web sites.

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with us under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from us and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We do not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Nokia Symbian Themes makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Blog Comments Policy:**

> Definitely we enjoy hearing from you about our designs and inspirations. However, to ensure that your valued comments rather enhance and not detract from the blog, we’ve created a formal comment policy which we hope you will follow..
> 
> Comment Moderation
> 
> In order to maintain unique integrity about its content,  **some comments, trackbacks, and pingbacks made to the Nokia Symbian Themes blog are sometimes moderated.** We work to review and approve comments as quickly as possible, but please kindly do not resubmit your comment if it does not appear right away.
> 
> Language, Length, and Format
> 
> Nokia Symbian Themes focuses primarily on Nokia users or potential Nokia users. That being said, please always avoid harsh language and the use of profanity and obscenity. Threatening language is absolutely not allowed nor will it be tolerated.
> 
> If one of our themes makes you feel so excited that you absolutely want to rip that theme apart and delete it forever (cause it sucks according to you) then feel free to publish a post in your own blog about it and leave a trackback to the theme we published.
> 
> Your comments are always welcome but please do not use excessive paragraphs when commenting and make it look longer. A short and sweet comment holds more value than a long one like this:
> 
> Thanks!
> 
> Thanks again! Bye!
> 
> (Know what we mean? We hope you do 
> 
> Linking To Your Site and Others
> 
> All links going out of the comments box is of rel=nofollow. And because of excessive spams we have implemented auto moderation for comments that provide a link to any url with the comment itself and not in the url box. Of course, if it is not spam, be sure that we will approve it right away.
> 
>  **Please double check your links** , because any link which returns an error or leads to a site under construction or cannot load might be removed.
> 
> Signatures within Comments
> 
> Adding a signature is completely optional. If you decide to include one, please keep it short (2 line maximum) and you can add a link to your website, however in that case please give it some time for moderation and please do not resubmit..
> 
> You are most welcome to add your website’s link in the designated URL box just below your name and e-mail address.
> 
>   * Unacceptable:  
> 
>
>> Captain Eugene
>> 
>> Owner of Eugene’s Website
>> 
>> http://www.eugeneswebsite.com/
>> 
>> Please visit some time
> 
>   * Acceptable:  
> 
>
>> Captain Eugene
>> 
>> Owner of Eugene’s Website
> 
> 

> 
>  **Also, if you leave an anchor text in the name box, then please include a signature name (your real name) when finishing up the comment. Otherwise, addressing to you is really difficult.**
> 
> Subscribing To Comments Via E-mail
> 
> In order to receive notification of comments left after yours, it is essential that you provide a valid and working e-mail address. To sign up for follow up comments, make sure to tick the check mark next to “Notify me of follow up comments via e-mail” before submitting your valued comment.
> 
> E-mail Addresses
> 
> Please use a valid e-mail address when commenting on the blog. It will NEVER be displayed unless you type it in the body of your comment voluntarily and you will not be subscribed to any mailing list by leaving a comment so always leave your comments  . However, if you use an invalid e-mail address your comment will be deleted.
> 
> Editing Comments
> 
> we do reserve the right to edit or delete comments if necessary. Excessive spelling and grammatical mistakes will be edited and serious edits will be notated at the end of the comment if required. But be sure that  **at no time will we attempt to alter the true meaning of your comment ever**.
> 
> Special Provisions For Comment Spam
> 
> We take comment spam pretty seriously so if you spam we will do my best to combat it accordingly by notifying the internet blacklists and your ISP in turn. So, please do not spam.
> 
> Conclusion about Comments:
> 
> Remember, it is only you who is responsible for your own words and comments. They are yours, however, by posting your comments to the blog you are granting me the right perpetually, to use, alter, and/or display them however we see fit.
> 
> Once your comment is submitted, we reserve the rights to it.

 **Licenses & Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website and the content found here within at <http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/disclaimer>

You must comply with two of the following licenses:

[Creative Commons 3.0 Share Alike:](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0) It specifies our (developer) right and expresses the legal right we have on our developed applications or themes.

and

[Symbian OS:](http://developer.symbian.com/wiki/display/pub/Licence) Any software’s right when it is developed, signed and licensed under the Symbian OS Platform.

Please refer to [our page](http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/dmca) regarding the DMCA Act for more information about any intellectual rights the developers have.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on March 14, 2009

 **Owner’s Words:**

Here is an honest truth from the owner and blogger of Chaos Inc.:

“I respect your privacy and I personally feel that one user shall know their online rights. I also feel that statistics matter because it will help develop the entire online and e-commerce market. I never engage with ad networks that entices people to do something and uses the info in an illegal way. Hence I recommend you to always know your rights and liabilities before you surf on the net or

simply try someone’s service out. Personally I feel that most of the bigger ad networks like Google, Yahoo, DoubleClick, MSN, TribalFusion, Admob etc will not hamper or tamper any info wrongly without thinking about the users or publishers and they will deliver the readers, publishers and visitors with all the good stuff while respecting their rights. Hence I never engaged myself with advertisers outside a very few. ”

But, still you should check out their policies in case you want to know more about privacy.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions or you have any feedback regarding this privacy policy then you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.nokiasymbianthemes.com/

Ishtiaq Saddam

19 Naya Paltan

Dhaka, Dhaka 1000

Bangladesh

or E-mail us at:

Mail The Owner

If you have any questions and comments about our Privacy Policy please contact us!

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
